

Tang Xuan Thao

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

About Me

A passionate software engineer with 3+ years of well-rounded experience in building web applications.

An effective team player offering extraordinary analytical skills and the important ability to think critically.

Contact

tang.xuanthao1996@gmail.com

(+84) 90 656 1545

https://fr0stf0x.github.io

Skills













Work Experience

Zigvy Corporation

June 2020 - Feb 2022

Software Engineer

- Work as a team leader and full-stack developer in many projects.
- Work closely with client and product owner to collect and understand requirements.
- Make weekly plans and implement features with team members.
- Code review and release applications.

ANTS Programmatic

Mar 2019 - May 2020

Frontend Executor

- Work in a frontend team to build an application for data aggregation, visualization and automated reporting using ReactJS.
- Work in a NodeJS team with another PHP back-end team and DB team to implement Restful APIs using ExpressJS, Redis, ElasticSearch and RabbitMQ.
- Build a system for monitoring company applications using ReactJS.
- Monthly seminar about technologies.

FPT Software

Apr 2018 - Aug 2018

Intern Web Developer

- Learn about software development process.
- Build a mock-up Interview process management system with HTML, CSS, Javascript and Spring Framework at backend.

Education and Certificates

Bachelor of Computer Science Aug 2015 - May 2021

Ton Duc Thang University

Major in Software Engineer GPA: 7.1/10

IIG Vietnam Apr 2021 - Apr 2023

TOEIC - 790/990

Axon Active Apr 2018

Agile Software Development with Scrum